You can come in.
入っていいよ
Excuse me. Yes, I'm tired of waiting.
失 礼します そうよ、待ちくたびれちゃったよ お待たせ
Yes, Master, cute or not, it's getting cold.
しました、 ご主人様 可愛いないかわらずね 寒いなってきたね
Well then, you can come in and load your things.
じゃあ さ、入っちゃって荷物を積み込んじゃっていい
of?
の?
Come over here. It's a nice hotel. Wow.
こ っちおいで いいホテルでしょ すごい、
It's a good hotel.
いいホテルです 入
I got it
れ ました
My boobs have gotten bigger again. I wonder if they've gotten bigger. I'm giving everyone a massage.
また おっぱい大きくなったんじゃん なったかな みんなに揉ま
It's getting rubbed a lot.
れて るもんね いっぱい揉まれてるもんね
Have you gotten used to it since the beginning?
最 初よりはさ 慣れてきた?
gradually
徐々に
The hand is
手 は
That's right, I'm going off track, if you're going to deal with sex,
そう 脱線してるんだよ 性処理するならさ、
I like girls like that, like I always want to use my body.
あんな子がいいみたいな いつも体使いたいみたい
I've been waiting too long. I'm thirsty now.
な 待ち続き過ぎてさ 喉が渇いてから
Shut your mouth.
さ 口を閉じて
Couldn't you let me do this?
こんな にさせられなかったの?
For the first time, close your thumbs.
初めて じゃあ親指を閉めて
I went to sleep again
もう 一回寝まして
No really?
ない ほんと?
Suck it all in your mouth
口の中さ、全部吸って
I was able to do it now.
でき るようになっていたじゃん
Just a little while ago, some water spilled on me, so lick it a little.
さ っきさ、水が こぼれちゃったからさ ちょっと舐めて 舐
keep it clean
めて きれいにして
Take out your cute baby, turn around a little, and move it backwards.
可愛 いの出して ちょっと後ろ向いて 後ろ向きに動かして
Minagi-san
み なぎさん
Do you understand that this is the only real master you have?
本当 のご主人様はこれだけだから 分かってる?
What am I? What am I?
自分はさ 俺は何?
What is your husband?
ご主人様は何?
I'm your master's girl. I'm also your master's girl. I'm your master's girl.
ご主人様の女の子です 私もご主人様の女の子です 私はご主人様
the girl
の 女の子です
Did you get it wet?
濡 らしてきた?
Did you get it properly wet?
ちゃんと濡らしてきた?
I got it wet
濡らしてきました
It's not like I'm going to give up on this friend, right? It's just me today.
この 仲間にさ、ご放育した後じゃないよね 今日俺だけのやつ
No, there, do a double piece.
して ない いや、そこでさ ダブルピースしてさ
Today too, my master will let me have a lot of fun with him.
今日 もご主人様に いっぱい ご放育させていただきますって
Today too, I will let my master take care of you a lot.
今日 もご主人様に いっぱいご放育させて いただきます
happy?
嬉 しい?
I'm glad you're growing up
大きくなってて 嬉しい
It's a really good animation and beautiful
です すごい良いアニション 綺麗な
There was a crow, it was cute
カ ラスいた 可愛い
happy?
嬉 しい?
I'm happy
嬉しいです
How do you keep your home clean?
お ちみちはどうやって 綺麗にするんですか?
Clean your mouth with your mouth.
おちみちは お口で綺麗にします おち
Michi cleans herself with her mouth, right?
み ちはお口で綺麗にするんだよね
Yes, I think it's beautiful.Next time, it's Shirimp Killy.
はい 綺麗だって感じ 次は シリンプキリーでしょ
It's okay, isn't it?
や ばいでしょ
Like before, facing backwards
さ っきみたいに 後ろ向きで
couple
カ ップル
Next time, make yourself comfortable.
次 は 気持ちよくしてください
I'm too good.
私 は よ すぎている
you are too good
あなたはよすぎます
you are big
あなたは大
I think it's weird.
変 だと思う
I think you're having a hard time.
あなたは大変だと思う
Elder Sister,
姉さん、
your husband's
ご 主人の
explained in the bible
聖 書に説明
Please do so.
して ください
Father, please explain to my Bible.
ご主人様の父は、私の聖書に説明してください
It feels so good, doesn't it?
気持ちよすぎでしょ
Well then,
じゃあさ、
So, give your breasts a break.
そ こでさ、ちょっとおっぱい休んで
Would you like to drink in your room?
部屋で飲むか
Uuuuuu
ううう
Uuuuuuuuuuu
う うう
No, it's a really good bunko.
いや ー、本当にいいバンコだもん
Well, let's be the most peaceful.
じゃあさ、最もピースしながらさ
I will do the carpentry method.
大工法をさせていただきます